WOW, THAT RIPPED.
THAT RIPPED REAL NICE.
HOW MANY TIMES
DO I HAVE TO TELL YOU--
YOU TURN AND SLIDE?
YOU KNOW?
TURN AND SLIDE.
YOU DON'T TURN AND SLIDE.
YOU THROW IT OUT.
I'M TIRED OF HAVING
TO GET A TETANUS SHOT
EVERY TIME I GET DRESSED.
WELL, WE'RE NOT
THROWING IT OUT.
I BUILT THIS THING
WITH MY OWN HANDS.
ALL RIGHT.
HOW 'BOUT WE...
HOW 'BOUT
WE SELL IT?
ALL RIGHT.
BUT YOU'RE GOING
TO HAVE TO TELL THEM.
DO YOU MIND IF WE STICK YOU
IN A DIFFERENT CABINET?
THEY SEEM ALL
RIGHT WITH IT.
♪ SO NO ONE TOLD YOU ♪
♪ LIFE WAS GONNA BE THIS WAY ♪
♪ YOUR JOB'S A JOKE,
YOU'RE BROKE ♪
♪ YOUR LOVE LIFE'S D.O.A. ♪
♪ IT'S LIKE YOU'RE ALWAYS
STUCK IN SECOND GEAR ♪
♪ WHEN IT HASN'T BEEN YOUR DAY ♪
♪ YOUR WEEK, YOUR MONTH,
OR EVEN YOUR YEAR ♪
♪ BUT I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ WHEN THE RAIN
STARTS TO POUR ♪
♪ I'LL BE THERE FOR YOU ♪
♪ LIKE I'VE BEEN THERE BEFORE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE YOU'RE THERE
FOR ME, TOO. ♪
( machine beeps )
Hey, Monica. It's Chip.
YES!
WHO'S CHIP?
SHH!
It was good running into you
at the bank today,
so here's my number-- 555-9323.
Give me a call. Later.
"CHIP" IS CHIP MATTHEWS.
THE GUY WHO TOOK
RACHEL TO THE PROM?
WHY IS HE CALLING YOU?
BECAUSE I RAN INTO HIM
AT THE BANK.
HE IS STILL SO CUTE.
MONICA, YOU'RE SO LUCKY.
HE'S LIKE THE MOST
POPULAR GUY IN SCHOOL!
I KNOW!
CHIP? HI. IT'S MONICA.
'KAY.
OKAY.
OKAY. GOOD-BYE.
OH, MY GOD, WE JUST HAD
THE BEST CONVERSATION.
I WAS JUST LEAVING.
GOOD,
'CAUSE I'VE GOT
A PRODUCT REPORT TO READ.
IT'S LIKE EIGHT PAGES.
I HOPE I DON'T FALL ASLEEP.
WHY? DID YOU WRITE IT?
WHOA.
LOOK AT THAT.
CHIP MATTHEWS CALLED.
WONDER WHAT HE WANTS.
WELL, UH, ACTUALLY...
I BET HE SENSED
THAT I WAS READY TO HAVE SEX
WITH ANOTHER GUY.
WELL, UM...
WHY DON'T YOU
GIVE HIM A CALL?
OKAY.
( clearing throat )
ARE YOU SURE
YOU WANT TO HEAR THIS?
OH, I'M SURE.
CHIP. HI. IT'S RACHEL.
RACHEL GREEN.
YEAH. UM,
YOU LEFT ME A MESSAGE?
YES, YOU DID.
MY ROOMMATE WROTE IT DOWN.
MONICA GELLER?
OH.
OH, THAT'S RIGHT.
HE CALLED
TO ASK OUT MONICA.
OHH. THAT'S-- THAT'S
GOT TO BE EMBARRASSING.
♪ DUMB DRUNKEN BITCH! ♪
( scattered applause )
THANK YOU.
THANKS.
NOW, HERE'S
A QUESTION.
WHERE'D YOU GUYS
GET "THE FINEST OAK
EAST OF THE
MISSISSIPPI"?
UH-UH. FIRST YOU TELL US
WHERE YOU GOT
THE PRETTIEST LACE
IN ALL THE LAND.
I'M READING YOUR AD.
LOOKS GOOD, HUH?
YEAH.
"STUNNING ENTERTAINMENT
CENTER, FINE..."
"FINE ITALIAN
CRAFTSMANSHIP."
OH, MY GOD. YOU GUYS ARE SELLING
THE ENTERTAINMENT CENTER?
WHY? I LOVE THAT THING.
YOU WANT IT?
EWW!
NO!
UH, GEPPETTO?
$5,000?
ARE YOU INSANE?
HEY, THE AD ALONE
COST 300 BUCKS.
ALL RIGHT, LOOK.
I'M CHANGING IT TO $50
OR YOUR BEST OFFER.
WHAT KIND OF PROFIT IS THAT?
AND YOU CALL YOURSELF
AN ACCOUNTANT?
NO.
OH.
WHAT DO YOU DO?
I CAN'T BELIEVE YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT I DO FOR A LIVING.
I ACTUALLY DON'T.
SOMETHING TO DO WITH...?
OH, MY GOD! NO!
SHOO, KITTY! NO!
NO, NO, NO. SHOO!
COME ON, YOU.
COME ON.
YOU'RE CRAZY.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT?
NOTHING. NOTHING.
WHAT? WHAT'S WRONG?
I JUST...
I JUST HAVE THIS
REALLY STRONG FEELING THAT...
THIS CAT IS MY MOTHER.
YOU MEAN THE MOM
YOU MET IN MONTAUK?
SHE WAS A CAT?
NO. NO, NO,
SHE WAS A HUMAN LADY.
THIS IS THE SPIRIT
OF MY MOM, LILY--
THE ONE THAT KILLED HERSELF.
ARE YOU SURE SHE'S IN THE CAT,
OR HAVE YOU BEEN TAKING
YOUR GRANDMA'S
GLAUCOMA MEDICINE AGAIN?
NO, DR. SKEPTISMO.
I'M SURE.
FIRST OF ALL, OKAY,
THERE'S THE FEELING.
OKAY, AND FOR ANOTHER,
HOW 'BOUT THE FACT
THAT SHE WENT INTO
MY GUITAR CASE?
WHICH IS LINED WITH ORANGE FELT.
MY MOTHER'S FAVORITE FISH
WAS ORANGE ROUGHY.
CATS LIKE FISH.
HI, MOMMY.
OH! I HAVEN'T SEEN
THIS SMILE IN 17 YEARS.
DUDE, PHOEBE'S MOM'S
GOT A HUGE PAIR...
LET IT GO.
HEY.
UM, WHEN WERE YOU
GOING TO TELL ME
THAT YOU'RE GOING OUT
WITH CHIP MATTHEWS?
NOW.
IS IT OKAY IF I GO OUT
WITH CHIP MATTHEWS?
NO, IT'S NOT OKAY.
I CAN'T BELIEVE
YOU WOULD WANT TO,
AFTER WHAT HE DID TO ME.
WHAT? THAT LITTLE THING
AT THE PROM?
MONICA, I COULDN'T FIND
HIM FOR TWO HOURS.
HE WAS HAVING SEX
WITH AMY WELSH.
COME ON, THAT WAS
BACK IN HIGH SCHOOL.
HOW COULD THAT
STILL BOTHER YOU?
WHY, OF ALL PEOPLE,
DO YOU HAVE TO GO
OUT WITH CHIP?
LOOK, YOU AND I WENT
TO DIFFERENT HIGH SCHOOLS.
THAT DOESN'T HELP ME
BECAUSE WE WENT TO
THE SAME HIGH SCHOOL.
YOU WENT TO ONE
WHERE YOU WERE POPULAR
AND YOU GOT TO RIDE OFF
ON CHIP'S MOTORCYCLE
AND WEAR
HIS LETTERMAN JACKET.
I WENT TO ONE WHERE
I WORE A BAND UNIFORM
THEY HAD TO HAVE
SPECIALLY MADE.
THAT SPECIALLY MADE?
IT WAS A PROJECT FOR ONE
OF THE HOME EC CLASSES.
OH, MY GOD.
THEY TOLD US THAT
WAS FOR THE MASCOT.
BACK THEN, I THOUGHT
THAT I WOULD NEVER,
EVER GET THE CHANCE
TO GO OUT
WITH A CHIP MATTHEWS
AND NOW HE'S... HE'S CALLED
ME UP AND ASKED ME OUT
AND THE FAT GIRL INSIDE ME
REALLY WANTS TO GO.
I OWE HER THIS.
I NEVER LET HER EAT.
OH, YOU GO
OUT WITH HIM.
OH, REALLY?
YEAH.
JUST, IF IT'S POSSIBLE
COULD YOU LEAVE HIM SOMEWHERE
AND GO HAVE SEX
WITH ANOTHER GUY?
I'LL TRY.
YOU GUYS HAVING
ANY LUCK GETTING RID
OF THE ENTERTAINMENT CENTER?
THERE WERE A COUPLE
CALLS LAST NIGHT
BUT I DON'T THINK ANY OF THEM
ARE GOING TO WORK OUT.
YES, JOEY HAS A VERY
CAREFUL SCREENING PROCESS.
APPARENTLY, NOT EVERYONE
IS QUALIFIED TO OWN
WOOD AND NAILS.
STOP IT. STOP IT.
SHE KEEPS SQUIRMING
AND TRYING TO GET AWAY--
JUST LIKE WHEN SHE WAS ALIVE.
SO, PHEEBS, HOW LONG
IS YOUR MOM GOING TO BE WITH US?
WELL, I'M NOT SURE.
I MEAN, I GUESS UNTIL SHE,
YOU KNOW, GETS USED TO THE FACT
THAT THERE'S,
YOU KNOW, A NEW MOM.
YOU KNOW, I THINK SHE'S WORRIED
THAT SHE'S GOING TO...
SHE'S GOING
TO BE REPLACED.
WELL, THAT'S NOT GOING
TO HAPPEN, IS IT? NO.
OKAY, I HAVE TO RETURN
A CALL IN THE OTHER ROOM.
WHY CAN'T YOU USE
THE PHONE IN HERE?
WELL, I'M RETURNING A CALL
FROM A CERTAIN MOM
AT THE B-E-A-C-H.
I JUST SPELLED
THE WRONG WORD.
SO, GUYS, AM I CRAZY,
OR DOES PHOEBE'S MOM
REMIND ANYONE ELSE
OF A CAT?
ROSS, DON'T START.
COME ON.
YOU CAN'T TELL ME
YOU ACTUALLY BELIEVE
THAT THERE'S A WOMAN
INSIDE THAT CAT.
I BELIEVE IT.
NO, YOU DON'T.
YES, I DO.
NO, YOU D...
YOU KNOW WHAT?
YOU'RE NOT GOING
TO SUCK ME INTO THIS.
OH, SURE, I AM--
BECAUSE YOU ALWAYS
HAVE TO BE RIGHT.
I DO NOT ALWAYS HAVE...
OKAY, OKAY.
JURASSIC PARK COULD HAPPEN.
WOW. THAT'S, UH...
THAT'S PRETTY NICE.
PRETTY NICE?
YOU'LL HAVE TO
PARDON MY ROOMMATE.
HE WANTED TO MARRY THIS.
WE DON'T HAVE 50 BUCKS.
BUT WOULD YOU BE WILLING
TO TRADE FOR IT?
WE GOT A CANOE.
YOU KNOW, I... I REALLY
DON'T THINK WE NEED A CANOE.
YOU GOT TO TAKE THE CANOE.
ALL RIGHT, JUST...
JUST TAKE THE
ENTERTAINMENT CENTER
AND THEN WHEN
YOU GET HOME
THROW THE CANOE AWAY.
WE'RE NOT
THROWING IT AWAY.
I BUILT THAT CANOE.
GOOD FOR YOU!
YOU GUYS, YOU'RE NEVER
GOING TO BELIEVE
WHAT I JUST FOUND TACKED
UP ON A TELEPHONE POLE.
LOOK KIND OF FAMILIAR?
APPARENTLY, PHOEBE'S MOTHER
ALSO GOES BY THE NAME JULIO.
YOU GUYS, THERE'S A LITTLE GIRL
IN SOHO LOOKING FOR THIS CAT.
I MEAN, YOU KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS?
YEAH, A $200 REWARD
SPLIT FIVE WAYS.
DO WE HAVE TO TELL HER?
YES, WE HAVE TO TELL HER.
OH, BUT IT'S
MADE HER SO HAPPY.
LITTLE GIRL
MISSES HER CAT.
CRAZY LADY THINKS HER
MOTHER IS IN A CAT.
OKAY. YOU KNOW WHAT?
I HAVE TO HAVE DINNER
WITH MY SON.
CAN I TRUST WHEN YOU SEE PHOEBE,
YOU WILL TELL HER?
YES.
YEAH.
THANK YOU.
I HATE IT
WHEN ROSS IS RIGHT.
HE IS RIGHT, ISN'T HE?
HEY, YOU KNOW WHAT? I THINK
THIS MIGHT BE ONE OF THE TIMES
WHEN HE'S WRONG.
YOU THINK?
OH, NO. HE'S RIGHT.
HI.
HEY.
UH, PHEEBS...
ABOUT YOUR MOM...
YEAH?
HOW'S THAT GOING?
SO GREAT.
OH, WE TOOK A NAP
TOGETHER TODAY.
MY MOM FELL ASLEEP
ON MY TUMMY AND PURRED.
THAT'S SO SWEET.
I'M GOING TO GET
SOME COFFEE.
OKAY.
HUH? WHAT'D YOU SAY, JOE?
I'LL BE RIGHT THERE.
PHEEBS...
I JUST FEEL SO... OH...
ALL RIGHT, ALREADY. GEEZ!
I'M COMING ALREADY.
( knock at door )
NOT YET, NOT YET,
NOT YET, NOT YET
NOT YET!
HELLO, CHIP.
HEY, RACH, HOW YOU DOING?
I'M GREAT. I'M GREAT.
GOT A GREAT JOB
AT BLOOMINGDALE'S
I HAVE WONDERFUL FRIENDS
AND EVEN THOUGH I'M NOT
SEEING ANYONE RIGHT NOW
I'VE REALLY NEVER FELT
BETTER ABOUT MYSELF.
SO, UH, MONICA READY YET?
SHE'LL BE OUT
IN A SECOND.
SO, CHIP, HOW'S,
UM, AMY WELSH?
AMY WELSH?
WOW. I HAVEN'T SEEN HER SINCE...
SO... MONICA ABOUT READY?
THIS IS THE UNIT
FOR YOU, MY FRIEND--
STURDY CONSTRUCTION,
TONS OF STORAGE COMPARTMENTS
SOME BIG ENOUGH
TO FIT A GROWN MAN.
WHAT?
OH, YEAH. I GOT
IN THERE MYSELF ONCE.
MY ROOMMATE BET ME
FIVE BUCKS THAT I COULDN'T
AND THEN HE STUCK A BOARD
THROUGH THE HANDLES
AND LOCKED ME IN-- YEAH.
IT WAS FUNNY TILL I STARTED
FEELING LIKE I WAS IN A COFFIN.
NO, YOU...
YOU CAN'T FIT
IN THAT THING.
THAT'S NOT DEEP ENOUGH.
OH, YEAH?
IF I CAN'T
I'LL KNOCK FIVE BUCKS
OFF THE PRICE OF THE UNIT.
YOU HAVE YOURSELF
A DEAL.
OKAY.
SEE? I TOLD YOU.
SOMETIMES I COME IN HERE
JUST TO GET AWAY FROM IT.
HEY, A NICKEL!
HERE WE ARE.
OH, MY GOD,
YOU STILL HAVE THE CHIPPER.
THE WHAT?
THAT'S WHAT WE USED
TO CALL YOUR MOTORCYCLE
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
YOU KNOW, A MOTORCYCLE'S
A CHOPPER
AND YOU'RE CHIP.
NEVER MIND.
NO. I THINK IT'S CUTE.
WOW.
A LIPPER FROM THE CHIPPER.
SO, YOU STILL IN TOUCH WITH
ANYONE FROM HIGH SCHOOL?
UM, THERE'S RACHEL,
AND, UM...
I THINK THAT'S IT.
HOW ABOUT YOU?
OH, YEAH, I STILL HANG
WITH SIMMONS AND ZANA
AND I SEE SPINDLER A LOT
AND LEVINE AND KELLY
AND I RUN INTO GOLDIE
FROM TIME TO TIME.
STICK, BROWN,
ZOLKOV, McGUIRE
J.T., BEARDSLEY...
IS THAT ALL?
YOU KNOW, AFTER HIGH SCHOOL
YOU JUST KIND OF LOSE TOUCH.
OH, YEAH, I RAN
INTO RICHARD DORFMAN.
OH, HOW IS HE?
NOT SO GOOD.
ME AND SIMMONS
GAVE HIM A WEDGIE.
ISN'T HE AN ARCHITECT NOW?
YEAH, THEY STILL
WEAR UNDERWEAR.
OH, MY GOD!
WHAT?!
ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
YEAH.
WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, MAN! HE PROMISED
HE WOULDN'T TAKE THE CHAIRS.
WHAT THE HELL HAPPENED?
HOW WERE YOU LOCKED IN THERE?
WHERE THE HELL'S
ALL OF OUR STUFF?
WELL, THIS GUY CAME BY
TO LOOK AT THE UNIT
AND HE SAID HE DIDN'T
THINK IT WAS BIG ENOUGH
TO FIT A GROWN MAN.
SO, YOU GOT IN
VOLUNTARILY?
I WAS TRYING
TO MAKE A SALE.
OH, MAN. IF I EVER
RUN INTO THAT GUY AGAIN,
YOU KNOW WHAT
I'M GOING TO DO?
BEND OVER?!
( chuckling )
AND THEN ZANA
JUST LET ONE RIP!
NOT THAT I DON'T ENJOY
TALKING ABOUT PEOPLE
WE WENT TO HIGH SCHOOL
WITH, 'CAUSE I DO
BUT MAYBE WE COULD TALK
ABOUT SOMETHING ELSE.
LIKE YOU.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHERE YOU WORK.
YOU KNOW WHERE I WORK.
I DO?
THE MOVIE THEATER.
YOU USED TO COME IN
ALL THE TIME.
YOU STILL WORK
AT THE MULTIPLEX?
LIKE I'D GIVE UP THAT JOB.
FREE POPCORN AND CANDY
ANYTIME I WANT?
I CAN GET YOU FREE POSTERS
FOR YOUR ROOM.
THANKS. I'M SET.
DO YOU STILL LIVE
WITH YOUR PARENTS?
YEAH, BUT I CAN STAY OUT
AS LATE AS I WANT.
WOW. THEY REALLY
GOT YOU GUYS--
YOUR TV, THE CHAIRS.
YEAH, YOUR MICROWAVE,
THE STEREO...
OH, MAN, HE TOOK
THE FIVE OF SPADES!
OH, NO, NO. HERE IT IS.
OH, MY GOD.
WHAT HAPPENED?
OH, UM, JOEY WAS BORN
AND THEN 28 YEARS LATER,
I WAS ROBBED.
SO HOW WAS YOUR DATE?
WELL, YOU KNOW HOW I
ALWAYS WANTED TO GO OUT
WITH CHIP MATTHEWS
IN HIGH SCHOOL?
WELL, TONIGHT,
I ACTUALLY WENT OUT
WITH CHIP MATTHEWS
IN HIGH SCHOOL.
OH, HONEY, I'M SORRY.
NO, IT'S OKAY. NOT ONLY DID I
GET TO GO OUT WITH CHIP MATTHEWS
I GOT TO DUMP
CHIP MATTHEWS.
OH, THAT'S SO GREAT.
I KNOW.
HEY.
SO, UH, WHAT DID THE
INSURANCE COMPANY SAY?
OH, THEY SAID,
"YOU DON'T HAVE INSURANCE HERE
SO STOP CALLING US."
YOU DIDN'T TELL HER?
OKAY, FINE.
PHEEBS.
YEAH, HI.
HI.
LISTEN, UH...
THIS CAT BELONGS
TO A LITTLE GIRL.
ALL RIGHT? THERE ARE FLYERS
ALL OVER THE PLACE.
I'M SORRY, SWEETIE.
HEY, WE CAN TAKE HER BACK
WITH YOU IF YOU WANT.
OH. HM-MMM.
BUT YOU KNOW,
SHE CHOSE TO FIND ME.
I MEAN, I HAVE TO RESPECT
HER DECISION, RIGHT?
IT'S A GOOD CALL.
RIGHT.
NO, NO! HEY!
ENOUGH IS ENOUGH!
LOOK, I AM SORRY
THAT YOU FEEL GUILTY
OR WHATEVER ABOUT SPENDING
TIME WITH YOUR NEW MOM
BUT THIS IS NOT
YOUR OLD MOM.
THIS IS A CAT, OKAY?
JULIO THE CAT.
NOT MOM. CAT.
OKAY.
ROSS, HOW MANY PARENTS
HAVE YOU LOST?
NONE.
THEN YOU DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT FEELS LIKE
WHEN ONE OF THEM
COMES BACK
DO YOU?
I BELIEVE
THIS IS MY MOTHER.
EVEN IF I'M WRONG,
WHO CARES?
JUST BE A FRIEND, OKAY?
BE SUPPORTIVE.
I'M SORRY.
OKAY.
I DON'T KNOW WHAT TO SAY.
YOU COULD SAY YOU'RE
SORRY TO HER MOM.
I THINK SHE
WOULD LIKE THAT.
COME HERE, HERE,
COME HERE, COME HERE.
MRS. BUFFAY?
SORRY ABOUT
WHAT I SAID.
UM, IT WAS--
IT WAS INSENSITIVE
OF ME TO SAY THAT
YOU WERE JUST A CAT...
WHEN CLEARLY YOU ARE ALSO
THE REINCARNATED SPIRIT...
OF MY FRIEND'S MOTHER.
THANK YOU.
WE BOTH FORGIVE YOU.
HONEY, WHAT ARE YOU GOING
TO DO ABOUT THE LITTLE GIRL?
YEAH. OKAY, LISTEN...
UM, MOM, I HOPE YOU KNOW
THAT YOU STILL MEAN
A LOT TO ME
AND YOU'RE WELCOME
TO COME BACK ANYTIME.
PHEEBS, IF SHE COULD
COME BACK AS A COUCH
WE'D REALLY
APPRECIATE IT.
COME ON, MOM, I'M GOING
TO TAKE YOU HOME.
I'LL GO WITH YOU.
ME, TOO.
OH, YOU KNOW, I GOT
AN EXTRA FUTON.
DUDE, YOU DON'T
HAVE TO BRAG!
WE GOT NOTHING HERE!